Guide to the Little Bobby Duncan poster collection, 1985-1986 MS 899
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Little Bobby Duncan poster collection
1985-1986
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Duncan, Robert "Little Bobby"
MS 899
1.5 Linear Feet (1 oversize box)
This collection consists of printed scans and photocopies of posters created by Little Bobby Duncan for the Houston music venue, Rockefeller's.
Biographical / Historical
Robert "Little Bobby" Duncan attended Rice in the early 1970s. He was the first Homecoming King in 1970. He went on to be an artist. In the mid-1980s, he illustrated concert posters for Rockefeller's in Houston.
Content Description
This collection consists of printed scans and photocopies of posters created by Little Bobby Duncan for the Houston music venue, Rockefeller's.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research. Since there is not a formal deed of gift for this collection, it can only be viewed in the reading room and not duplicated.
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Obtained from Robert "Little Bobby" Duncan. This collection does not have a deed of gift. It is for research only.
Index Terms
Subjects
Music
Document Types
Rhythm and blues music; Blues (Music); Folk music; Folk-rock music; Jazz; Rock music
Places
Art
Subjects (Corporations)
Rockefeller's
- Series I: Posters
  - Leon Russell and Ezra Charles, 1985-07-12-1985-07-13 (Box 1)
  - Screamin' Jay Hawkins and Mighty Joe Young, 1985-07-26-1985-07-27 (Box 1)
  - Jorma Kaukonen, 1985-08-08 (Box 1)
  - B.B. King, 1985-08-21-1985-08-25 (Box 1)
  - Doctor John with the Night Tripper, 1985-09-20-1985-09-21 (Box 1)
  - Albert Collins, 1985-10-25 (Box 1)
  - Randy Newman, 1985-10-27 (Box 1)
  - The Sir Douglas Quintet, 1985-11-22 (Box 1)
  - The Nighthawks, 1985-12-12 (Box 1)
  - Big Twist and the Mellow Fellows with Coupe de Ville, 1985-12-31 (Box 1)
  - Bonnie Raitt, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Doc Watson, 1986-01-15 (Box 1)
  - John Lee Hooker with the Robert Cray Band, 1986-01-31 (Box 1)
  - Roomful of Blues, 1986-02-06-1986-02-07 (Box 1)
  - The Neville Brothers, 1986-03-01 (Box 1)
  - David Bromberg and Arlo Guthrie, 1986-03-11 (Box 1)
  - Mitch Ryder with David Wayne Kleb, 1986-03-17 (Box 1)
  - Delbert McClinton, 1986-04-04 (Box 1)
  - Wynton Marsalis, 1986-07-04-1986-07-05 (Box 1)
  - Nicolette Larson, 1986-08-11 (Box 1)
  - Sandra Bernhard, 1986-09-07 (Box 1)